Guide to the Thomas E. Packer Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Thomas E. Packer papers
1833-1864
MS 1010
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(1 box)
The papers consist of letters written to Packer from fellow teachers, family, and business associates, plus financial, legal, and miscellaneous papers. The correspondence covers the years 1851-1858, when Packer was teaching school in West Mystic, Connecticut; Brandon, Mississippi; and Mystic Bridge, Connecticut. The letters contain news about teaching, discussions of spiritual and intellectual concerns, and remarks about places visited.
Packer, Thomas E.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Whitlock's in 1954.
Scope and Contents
The Thomas E. Packer Papers, 1833-1864, consist of letters that Packer received and drafts or copies of a few letters that he wrote. In this period he taught school in Portersville (now West Mystic), Connecticut (1851-1852), Brandon, Mississippi (1852-1853), and Mystic Bridge, Connecticut (1853-), and he may have sold books and pens or merely supplied them to his pupils. His most frequent correspondents were fellow teachers: William Henry Potter (Y. 1840), who was principal of a college or academy in Brandon, Mississippi; Dudley A. Avery, who taught in Mystic Bridge, Connecticut, and Lyme, Ohio; Joseph H. Rindge, who taught in Mystic River, Connecticut; Andrew J. Welles, who taught in East Hartford and Glastonbury, Connecticut; and J. W. Eddy, who taught in Brandon, Mississippi, and West Haven and Fair Haven, Connecticut. Their letters contain news about teaching, discussions of spiritual and intellectual concerns, and occasional remarks about the places in which they lived. Packer's other principal correspondents were his friend Orlando Brown (1827-1904; Y. 1851m), his brother Freemasons, his Packer and Burrows relations, the companies that supplied him with pens and publications, and various people who advised him on settling his father's estate.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open for research.
Education, Secondary; Education; Teachers -- Connecticut; Teachers -- Mississippi; Brandon (Miss.) -- History; Connecticut; Groton (Conn.) -- History; Middle West; Mystic (Conn.) -- History; Southern States; Educators; Avery, Dudley A.; Brown, Orlando, 1827-1904; Eddy, J. W.; Packer, Thomas E.; Potter, William Henry, 1816-1887; Rindge, Joseph H.; Welles, Andrew J.
- Inventory, 1833-1864; 0.5; (1 box)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Orlando Brown to Thomas Packer, 1851 June 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Warren Bu[rton?] to Thomas Packer, 1851 July 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Orlando Brown to Thomas Packer, 1851 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Thomas Packer to "Cousin", 1851 July 22 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - S.S. Fitch to Thomas Packer, 1851 August 12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1851 October 16, [1851] October 28 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Andrew Welles to Thomas Packer, 1851 November 20 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1851 November 28, December 20 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - William H. Potter to "Bro." [Thomas Packer?](this letter is written at the bottom of the 1851 Dec 20 letter with a page added), 1852 January 5 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - D. A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1852 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Brown to Thomas Packer, 1852 January 30 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Henry Bill to Thomas Packer, 1852 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Andrew Welles to Thomas Packer, 1852 February 10 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1852 February 21 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - D. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1852 March 12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1852 April 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Andrew Welles to Thomas Packer, 1852 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1852 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - James D. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1852 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1852 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Andrew Welles to Thomas Packer, 1852 June 17 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1852 July 17-31 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Andrew Welles to Thomas Packer, 1852 August 17 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bolles Company to Thomas Packer, 1852 August 27 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - E.O. Hovey to Thomas Packer, 1852 August 31 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - D.A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1852 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - [Orlando?] Brown to Thomas Packer, 1852 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - D.A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1852 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Joseph Rindge to Thomas Packer, 1852 October 20 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Helen Packer to Thomas Packer, 1852 October 20 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - D.A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1852 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - John A. Fitch to Thomas Packer, 1852 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - [Orlando?] Brown to Thomas Packer, 1852 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Helen Packer to Thomas Packer, 1852 November 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - [H.O.S.?] Bailey to Thomas Packer, 1852 November 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Saphronia B[urrows?]to [Thomas Packer?], 1852 November 5 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1852 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Joseph Denison to Thomas Packer, 1852 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Joseph Rindge to Thomas Packer, 1852 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1852 November 22 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Nelson Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1852 [Nov?] 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1852 December 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - G.G. B(ailey) to Thomas Packer, 1852 December 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Nelson Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1852 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Joseph Denison to Thomas Packer, 1852 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Helen Packer to Thomas Packer, 1852 December 17 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Benjamin Brown to Thomas Packer, 1852 December 18 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Helen Packer to Thomas Packer, 1852 December 20 rec'd (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1852 December 20 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Thomas W. Russell to Thomas Packer, 1852 December 28 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Helen Packer to Thomas Packer, 1852 December 30 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Joseph Rindge to Thomas Packer, 1853 January 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 January 6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - G.G. Bailey to Thomas Packer, 1853 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Calista V. Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1853 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Nelson Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1853 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 January 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - H[elen?] G. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - J.G. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - [Pheb.?] M. Fish to [Thomas Packer?], 1853 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 January 26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Amos Watrous to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Joseph Rindge to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Helen Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 9 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - John G. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - H[elen?] G. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - G.S. Bailey to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 17 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Nelson Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 March 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma J. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 March 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma J. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 March 9, 1853 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - John G. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 March 17 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Thomas Packer to (Emma) Jane Packer, 1853 March 18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Delight Packer to Thomas Packer, [1853?] March 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma J. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 March 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Helen Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - John A. Fitch to Thomas Packer, 1953 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma J. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 March 30, 1853 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 April 7 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - G.W. [B.?] to Thomas Packer, 1853 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Calista Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1853 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Helen Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - [Rhodes?] Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1853 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Helen Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 April 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Andrew Welles to Thomas Packer, 1853 April 20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - John G. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 April 20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - H[elen?] Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 April 22 rec'd (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - John Fitch to Thomas Packer, 1853 May 8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - G.I. Bailey to Thomas Packer, 1853 May 9 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Helen Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 May 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma J. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - H[elen?] G. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Nelson Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1853 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Thomas Packer to (Emma) Jane Packer, 1853 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - John G. Packer to John Packer, 1853 May 29 rec'd (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma J. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 May 30 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - R[hodes?] Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1853 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Andrew Welles to Thomas Packer, 1853 June 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - G.S. Bailey to Thomas Packer, 1853 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma J. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 June 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - F. Gleason to Thomas Packer, 1853 June 24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dawson, Warren& Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1853 June 24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Hannah Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma J. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 June 27 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Thomas Packer to Emma Jane Packer, 1853 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma J. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Nelson Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1853 July 6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emma J. Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 July 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Helen Packer to Thomas Packer, 1853 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - F. Gleason to Thomas Packer, 1853 July 18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 July 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1853 July 19, 1853 July 26, 1853 July 28 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - [John W.?] to Thomas Packer, 1853 July 29 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 August 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - J.W. Eddy to Thomas Packer, 1853 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Andrew Welles to Thomas Packer, 1853 August 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1853 August 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - [H.D.?] Rice to Thomas Packer, 1853 August 25 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1853 September 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Samuel Coolidge to Thomas Packer, 1853 September 5 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1853 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1853 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1853 September 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - William Potter to Thomas Packer, 1853 September 18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1853 September 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - [James Savage?] to Thomas Packer, 1853 September 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 September [24?] rec'd, 1853 September 28 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - [William H. Potter?] to Thomas Packer, 1853 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - William H. Potterto Thomas Packer, 1853 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to: Thomas Packer, 1853 October 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - J.W. Eddy to Thomas Packer, 1853 October 14, 1853 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1853 October 22 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - J.W. Eddy to Thomas Packer, 1853 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1853 October 31, 1853 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1853 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - [Rt?] Denison to Thomas Packer, 1853 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1853 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - R.B. Fitch to Thomas Packer, 1853 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dawson, Warren, & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1853 November 22 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Thomas Packer to [Emma Jane Packer?], 1853 November 25 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - J.W. Eddy to Thomas Packer, 1853 November 28 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - R.B. Fitch to Thomas Packer, 1853 November 28 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1853 November 29, 1853 December 15 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - F. Gleason to Thomas Packer, 1853 December 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1853 December 26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1853 December 26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1854 January 25 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1854 January 30 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1854 February 5, 1854 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - William. H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1854 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - W. Fish to Thomas Packer, 1854 March 3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1854 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1854 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - W. Fish to Thomas Packer, 1854 March 21, 1854 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1854 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - W. Fish to Thomas Packer, 1854 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1854 April 11, 1854 13, 1854 17 rec'd, 1854 May 20, 1854 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1854 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1854 June 10, 20, July 5, 8 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - W. H. Edwards to Thomas Packer, 1854 July 17 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1854 July 19 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - W.H. Edwards to Thomas Packer, 1854 July 20, 24 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - J.W. Eddy to Thomas Packer, 1854 September 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1854 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - J.W. Eddy to Thomas Packer, 1854 September 17, 1854 September 21 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1854 September 27 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1854 October 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Thomas M. Clark to Thomas Packer, 1854 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1854 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - C.P. Chipman to Thomas Packer, 1854 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1854 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - William S. Fish to Thomas Packer, 1854 November 18, 20 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1854 November 30, December 7 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - J.F. Brennan to Thomas Packer, 1854 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1854 December 21 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1854 December 28 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - J.W. Eddy to Thomas Packer, 1855 January 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - [F.C. Leonard?) to Thomas Packer, 1855 January 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - George Scofield to Thomas Packer, 1855 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - J.F. Brennan to Thomas Packer, 1855 January 12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - J.W. Eddy to Thomas Packer, 1855 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Nelson Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1855 January 20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Jerome Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1855 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1855 February 17 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1855 February 24 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - [Warner Buhr?] to Thomas Packer, 1855 March 19 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - C. Schwartz to Thomas Packer, 1855 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1855 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - W. Buhr to Thomas Packer, 1855 April 20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1855 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - J.W. Eddy to Thomas Packer, 1855 June 10 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Albert Avery to Thomas Packer, 1855 June 11, 28 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1855 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1855 July 5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1855 July 6, 10, 13, 17, 20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - P. Brandyce to Thomas Packer, 1855 July 25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1855 July 26 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Albert Avery to Thomas Packer, 1855 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - William H. Potter to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - A.E. Stone to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - T.C. Stearns to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 17 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Starr & Co. to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - T.C. Stearns to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 22 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Albert L. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Starr & Co. to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - W.W. Montague to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 24 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - J.W. Jenks to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 24 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Starr & Co. to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - A.E. Stone to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - [T.B. Muir?] to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 27 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - L.I. Learned to Thomas Packer, 1855 August 31 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - George Scofield to Thomas Packer, 1855 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1855 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - [S.H.O.] to Thomas Packer, 1855 September 15 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1855 September 15, 20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Starr & Co. to Thomas Packer, 1855 September 21 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Oscar Cottrell to Thomas Packer, 1855 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1855 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - John G. Mott & Co. to Thomas Packer, 1855 September 27, 28 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Oscar Cottrell to Thomas Packer, 1855 October 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - J.S. Denison to Thomas Packer, 1855 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1855 October 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - J.W. Eddy to Thomas Packer, 1855 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Oscar Cottrell to Thomas Packer, 1855 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - A.E. Stone to Thomas Packer, 1855 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1855 November 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1855 November 10 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - A.E. Stone to Thomas Packer, 1855 November 11, 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Oscar Cottrell to Thomas Packer, 1855 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - George Packer to unknown recipient, 1855 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - George Scofield to Thomas Packer, 1855 November 22 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1855 November 24 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - J.D. Fish & Son to Thomas Packer, 1855 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1855 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - John G. Mott & Co. to Thomas Packer, 1855 November 30 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Eldridge [Spier?] to Thomas Packer, 1855 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - T. J. Coleman to Thomas Packer, 1855 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - [signiture unclear] to Thomas Packer, 1855 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1855 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dan Bailey to Thomas Packer, 1855 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Oscar Cottrell to Thomas Packer, 1855 December 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1855 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Samuel Parsons to Thomas Packer, 1855 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Oscar Cottrell to Thomas Packer, 1855 December 18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1855 December 18, 24 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - James McManus to Thomas Packer, 1856 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Higgins and Bradley to Thomas Packer, 1856 February 16 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1856 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - A.E. Stone to Thomas Packer, 1856 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - S.W. Wood to Thomas Packer, 1856 May 10 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1856 June 3, 11, 13, 30 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1856 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Le Huray & Co. to Thomas Packer, 1856 July 25 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - S.W. Wood to Thomas Packer, 1856 July 29 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - George Scofield to Thomas Packer, 1856 September 17 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Charles Houche to Thomas Packer, [1856?] September 21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1856 September 23, 27, October 9 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Warren Beebe to Thomas Packer, 1856 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - John G. Mott & Son to Thomas Packer, 1856 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Thomas Avery to Thomas Packer, 1856 November 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - R. J. Wilson to Thomas Packer, 1856 November 10 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - A. E. Harmon to Thomas Packer, 1856 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Warren Beebe to Thomas Packer, 1856 November 28 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1856 December 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - A.E. Harmon to Thomas Packer, 1856 December 26 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Nelson Burrows to Thomas Packer, 1857 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - T.D. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1857 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1857 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - W. Fish to Thomas Packer, 1857 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, 1857 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1857 June 19
    - Brother Parsons to Thomas Packer, 1857 June 23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - A.E. Harmon to Thomas Packer, 1857 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1857 July 11 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Warren, Ludden & Sollace to Thomas Packer, 1857 July 13 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - A.E. Harmon to Thomas Packer, 1857 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1857 August 14 (Box 1, Folder 7)